New York City.
If only everything down there
was really as peaceful
as it looks from up here.
Yeah, hold it right there!
Yeah ! Like I was saying,
you're gonna love working down here.
It's cool in the summer
and warm in the winter.
And uh, no office politics.
That sounds better than my last job,
I was in the television business.
TV?! Really!
Hey, my old TV gets these double
images, you know what I mean?
Hey maybe you could...
No, I was a TV executive.
Oh, hey you're better off down here.
Holy...
Wait it's got me! What?! Help!
Help!
Those eyes, they're after me!
What's this?!
Another satisfied graduated
of the New York City
cab driving academy?
Hit the brake!
Turn! Turn!
s01ep01 - Night of the Lizard
Sync and corrections by manu777
www.addic7ed.com
What was that all about?
The red eyes!
The red eyes they're after me!
Uh-uh... And did they belong
to little pink elephants?
No. Mister it was real!
It was real! I swear!
Yeah alright, fine!
Just don't let the cops
blame this one on me okay?
The red eyes... The red eyes!
Sure pal, whatever you say!
New York City, never a dull moment!
Well, guess it all goes with the job.
Peter, I have a new job for you.
You've always gotten
good shots of Spiderman, right?
Let's see
what you can do with the Lizard.
- The who?
- The Lizard, Parker.
If you'd ever get here on time,
maybe you'd know what was going on.
There've been reports
of a giant lizard down in the subways.
- In this town, who'd notice?
- I'd notice...
If this weren't serious Parker,
I wouldn't have gotten the assignment.
I don't know about that Brock,
you're just a reporter
I'd send in a wild goose chase.
It's not a wild goose chase,
smart mouth.
Look. Subway repairman. Missing.
His friend says the Lizard got him.
Boss, I've got those names for the
scientists who've worked with reptiles.
Good. Then you can
interview them for background.
Right. Closest one is at Empire State.
Name's Connors.
- Doctor Curt Connors?
- You know him Peter?
He's one of my teachers Mr. Robertson.
He's an expert in recombining DNA
and reptile mutagenics.
He's also a genius!
Yeah, yeah. Whatever.
You'll be the contact
with Connors from now on kid.
- But boss...
- The kid already knows him,
and besides, do you have any idea
what mutawhat's-it's are?
Uh...
Mr. Jameson I still think this whole
Lizard-thing is just a big hoax!
Parker! The first one
to get a photo of the Lizard
for my nightly news
gets a thousand dollar bonus.
Uh, colour or black and white?
A thousand dollars, I could
put it down on a new motorcycle.
Maybe a car! Wait 'til I tell Aunt May!
- Hey pretty lady! Why the frown?
- Nothing Peter, nothing at all.
I just... can't decide
what to make for dinner that's all.
Why does she always
keep things from me?
Look at these bills!
And here I am,
thinking of things to buy for myself.
She's been
like a mother to me for years!
It's time I paid her back.
And if I can't.
It's a thousand dollar bonus.
Spiderman will.
Just once I want an assignment
in some nice sunny suburb.
Huh anyway this lizard-thing
is probably just an urban myth.
Wait a minute!
Looks like I was myth-taken!
- Peter!
- Oh no. Not Deborah Whitman!
The little sister I never had...
or wanted.
Since when do you have night class?
In fact I've always thought of you
as having no class at all.
Nyuk nyuk.
It just so happens I've got
something to show Doc Connors.
- Oh, really? What?
- None of your... Hey!
Hmmm... Well that's interesting.
Obviously a reptilian
of the Squamata order.
But, look at the imprint
left by the heel!
It's an imprint. So?
Yes, but look how deep it is!
Lot of weight on it.
Well, maybe it's a very fat squamata!
Or maybe Peter, it walks on two legs!
- I knew that!
- You didn't... Hmph!
Shhh.
Something's wrong.
You're darn right,
you were suffocating me!
- Nice time for a brownout, eh?
- Uhh, no kidding.
The storm must be causing it.
Who's there? Who is it?
- No! Stay away!
- Dr. Connors? What's wrong?
- No, Deborah, wait!
- But it sounds like he needs help.
Aaaaah!
Peter!
Deborah!
Are you alright?
I got the wind knocked out of me.
What's that thing done to Doc Connors?
Stop! Come back!
Peter! Don't leave me here alone!
It's alright.
Everything's okay now
You were downright brave back there!
It was quite a surprise!
Why, Miss Whitman,
is that a compliment?
- From you?
- Don't push your luck, Peter!
What was that thing?
And why would it kidnap Dr. Connors?
Dr. Connors, I'm ready to proceed.
Temperature alpha.
Respiration alpha.
Life signs all
register normal, Dr. Connors.
If I'm right,
Mickey here is better than normal.
Hmm.
Look! Look! There it is!
A reptile's ability
to grow a new limb... in a mammal!
All because of a couple
of micrograms of reptile DNA,
and a neogenic recombinator!
- Incredible!
- No, Peter,
this is just the beginning.
When we do the same for human beings
when we can replace limbs
lost in accidents or during a war.
That would be incredible.
Why would anybody
want to kidnap Dr. Connors?
Mommy? Is daddy coming home?
I don't know, Billy, I... Aaaaah!
Stay away! Leave us alone!
Easy, Mrs. Connors!
I'm looking for the professor.
- No! I won't let you hurt my husband!
- Hurt him? I...
Noooo!
No! No! Please!
You're for real!
Just hold that pose, Smiley!
Whoa!
Great, there goes my 1000 dollar photo!
Bah. When am I gonna get the hang
of being a super-hero and
a photographer at the same time?
Good reflexes,
for a future handbag!
Now that you crawled out of your sewer,
maybe you'd better stick around.
Because I wanna know
what you did with Doc Connors
Now you're really making me mad!
- No daddy, stop!
- Billy...
"Daddy"?
Did I hear right?
Did he say "daddy"?
Yes. Yes that was Curt.
It all started with a device.
Curt called it
the "neogenic recombinator",
he used it on himself as an
experiment to make his arm grow again.
But it turned him into that...
that creature!
Why haven't you told anybody?
The police?
No! They'll think he's a freak!
They'll hunt him down and hurt him
...or worse.
I know how that goes.
But not If I can reach him first!
I'm so scared.
We'll keep this quiet,
as long as we can.
Uh-oh... We're not alone !
When I break this story
it'll be Pullitzer time!
Hang loose, Brock,
That webbing will melt
in a couple of hours.
- You can't do this!
- I already have!
I won't let you ruin Connors' life.
What, what!...
Mommy! Mommy!
Billy! Where's your mom?
Daddy came back and took her away!
Down here!
The sewers...
Listen, I'm gonna carry you to a
neighbors' house where you'll be safe,
then I'll go get your mom
and your dad too. OK?
OK,
but don't let anything happen to them.
Let me go! Let me go!
Ugh, what a slimy mess!
Why can't I be one of those
galaxy-helping superheroes?
Why do I end up in the sewers?
Ugh.
Whoa!
You don't find the Fantastic Four
in the sewer!
Or the Avengers!
Never have I seen the Avengers
in the sewer!
Or the Defenders!
Well, maybe the Hulk...
Quit griping, Parker.
You know what's really bothering you.
You're scared.
This Lizard creature is powerful
enough to tear you limb from limb!
But you can't even hurt him,
because trapped inside is your friend.
But I have to find him,
it's the only way to stop him!
..to save him!
Well isn't this the story of my life?
Put me down, stop!
No! Don't!
Gotta reach him fast.
Whoa! Not this fast!
Uh-oh, tilt.
Time to put on the brakes !
Argh. My webbing's
losing its consistency.
I better change cartridges soon.
The worst part of all this is,
I was the one who helped the
Doc with these experiments.
If it wasn't for me... Uh?
Save me! Save me!
The missing subway worker!
He's building some electrical thing,
he couldn't do it himself.
He needed my help, but I,
I got weak. No food, no sleep.
Aaaaaaaah!
- Hey, come back for me, ri-right?
- Hey, I'm the hero, remember?
*growls*
Why did you bring me here, Curt? Why?
- So we can be together.
- You're still my husband. I love you,
I want to be with you,
but not like this.
I... love you, too. I need you,
and I need your help, with this.
I need your hands to operate it for me.
Mine can't grasp.
The other human got weak, scared.
- What are you going to do with that?
- Don't be afraid, Margaret.
It'll transform you.
You'll be able to heal any wound.
Replace any limb.
First you, then everyone.
Once I connect the neogenic
recombinator to these
electrical conduits, I can reach
every home in the city!
Every man, woman and child!
I can transform all of them!
No more suffering, no more pain.
But Curt. After you transform everyone
we'll all be like you!
Of course. I'm the first of
a new race! A better race!
If you're so much better
why do you need my hands to help you?
You're not better.
Look what you've become!
No! You're twisting things!
I can make people well again.
And I won't stop for anything!
Not even for Billy?
- You want him to be like you too?
- My son... I have a son...
Sorry, Doc!
I'm doing this for Billy
as much as for you!
Oooh!
*growls*
His mind's all reptile now.
Mrs. Connors! Get away while you can!
He's dangerous!
No, don't touch that thing!
Mrs. Connors, run!
Aaah!
Oh, nooo.
Margaret. I'm sorry...
I'll only get one chance on this
or I'm lizard food.
Uh-oh! Jell time!
Curt...
Strange. So strange.
A week ago this creature
was a scientist.
My teacher. My friend.
He cared for people
and wanted to help them,
just as I do.
And now look at the both of us.
Fighting each other...
fighting for our lives!
Curt! Spider-man!
- Curt... Is he..?
- He'll be OK.
Ooh, thank heaven!
I'll help you carry him
out of here in a second.
But first I have to get something.
A thousand dollar photo!
Not too shabby.
And what's Eddie Brock
going to end up with?
An exclusive story
nobody's ever going to believe!
I tell you, JJ,
the Lizard is Curt Connors.
I would have had you out here earlier,
but Spiderman webbed me.
Dr. Connors is
a respected scientist, Brock.
And Peter Parker already
brought me photos of the Lizard
early this morning.
But I'll show you the Lizard himself!
- You better be right about this.
- Boss, if I'm wrong, I'll...
I'll, I'll eat today's issue of Bugle.
J. Jonah Jameson.
What brings you here this morning?
You want it cooked or raw?
Peter, where did you get this?
I sold an exclusive
photo to The Daily Bugle.
- Oh, dear.
- What's wrong?
Exactly how did you happen
to get this picture?
Well.. I...
- No hemming and hawing.
- Aunt May, I-I..
You followed Spider-man
into the sewer, didn't you?
Yeah...right.
It's cold and damp down there!
You probably got germs
incubating even as we speak.
You need some hot soup
and a good long rest.
A nice boy like you,
taking pictures in a sewer!
And what if that
horrible Spiderman had caught you?
Aunt May... She'd never understand.
Spider-man's already
caught me in his web.
And for better or worse
he and I are stuck together, forever.