( buzzing like a bee )
SPONGEBOB:
Wow, four stingers.
( buzzing )
Oh!
( girl yelling )
( yelling )
( gasps )
( grunting )
Where have I seen this before?
Here it is...
land squirrel.
That little squirrel
is in trouble.
Take that, you sorry old clam!
You need to learn some manners!
You're about as ugly
as homemade soup.
Hooray, land squirrel!
( growls )
Look out!
( grunting )
Hold on, little squirrel!
( karate yell )
Ho-ho-ho!
Ho-hee!
Hoy-ya!
You have fought well,
giant clam.
Prepare to be vanquished.
( yells, grunting )
Hey, I'm actually doing it.
( grunting )
( victorious yell )
Your shell is mine!
( grunts ):
Hold on there,
little square dude.
( karate yell )
( yells )
( clam whimpers )
Hey, you like karate, too.
( karate yelling )
Ha!
So, what's your name?
Sandy.
So, what... do...
you call... yourself?
( yelling ):
I'm... SpongeBob!
Well, SpongeBob...
take a gander at this.
( rumbling, cracking )
Oh.
Oh, yeah?
Watch this.
( yells )
( armpit-farts )
( giggles ):
I like you,
SpongeBob.
We could be tighter
than bark on a tree.
( karate yells )
Uh, I like you, too, Sandy.
Yow.
Say, uh, what is that thing
on your head?
That's my air helmet.
May I try it on?
Heck, no.
I need it to breathe.
I got to have my air.
Me, too!
I love air. Air is good.
No kidding?
Why, air is my middle name.
The more air, the better.
Can't get enough of that air.
( drawling ):
Shoot!
How about coming
over tomorrow for
tea and cookies then?
Don't be late.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Patrick!
Patrick, Patrick, Patrick!
What's air?
Huh?
I just met this girl.
She wears a hat full of... air.
Do you mean she "puts on airs"?
I guess so.
That's just fancy talk.
If you want to be fancy,
hold your pinky up like this.
The higher you hold it,
the fancier you are.
How's that?
Higher.
Like that?
Now, that's fancy!
They should call you
SpongeBob FancyPants!
Remember, when in
doubt, pinky out.
You can do it, SpongeBob.
I'll be watching.
Thanks, pal.
( rings bell )
Hello?
Hiya, Sandy.
It's me, SpongeBob.
Hold on a sec, I'll let you in.
( buzzing )
( whistling )
( drain gurgling )
( stifled whistling )
( blows raspberry )
( yelling ):
Sandy!
Open up!
Sandy! Sandy!
Sandy, something's gone
terribly wrong.
There's no water in...
...here.
SANDY:
'Course there's no water.
Nothing but air.
No water?
That ain't a problem, is it?
( karate yells )
Problem?
That's how I like my air.
( inhales deeply )
( gagging, coughing )
( weakly ):
With no water.
SANDY:
Well, all right.
I made Texas tea and cookies.
Well, come on in.
( karate yells )
( legs squeaking )
That's not in.
In!
( squeaking )
You're a funny little dude.
Come on, I'll give you
the grand tour.
So this is my own
private little
air bubble.
This air is the driest...
( gasps )
purest...
most airiest air
in the whole sea.
Oh, over there is my birdbath.
( chirping cheerily )
And that's my oak tree.
lt provides me
with extra air.
( chirping )
This dome is made of the
strongest polyurethane;
that's a fancy name for plastic.
Ain't that just the bee's knees?
Tell you what, weren't easy
getting here neither.
First, I...
( grunting )
( chirping angrily )
...that's my treadmill.
That's how I stay
in tiptop shape.
Oh, come on... let's
have that tea now.
( karate yells )
( gasps )
( knocking on dome )
Pinky, pinky!
( gasps weakly )
I brought you some flowers.
For me?
How sweet!
You okay?
( raspily ):
Yes.
I'm okay.
You know, you're the first
sea critter to ever visit.
I can't imagine why.
Can I get you anything?
Water would be nice.
I'm going to put these
in a vase.
Take your time.
( wild gasping )
I got to get out of here!
SANDY:
I like you, SpongeBob.
We could be tighter than bark
on a tree.
PATRICK:
When in doubt, pinky out.
I don't need water!
Water's for quitters!
I don't need it.
I don't need it,
Why, these flowers
are just beautiful.
They'll live much, much longer
in a vase full
of ice-cold water.
So tell me about yourself.
It must be fascinating
being a sea critter.
SpongeBob?
( timer dings )
Oh, there's the cookies.
Be right back.
SPONGEBOB ( thinking ):
l don't need it.
I don't need it.
I definitely don't need it.
( shouting ):
l need it!
( wheezing )
No, SpongeBob!
No, no, no!
Stop!
Pinky, pinky!
( yelling ):
I'm a quitter!
( SpongeBob wailing )
You can't leave now.
You'll blow it.
Air is not good, Patrick.
Air is not good.
You're just being shy.
Don't worry, buddy.
You're doing fine.
( panting heavily )
I won't let you blow... this.
( wheezing )
( gagging )
What kind of place is this?!
There's no water in here!
I tried to tell you!
We got to get out of here!
You're doing it wrong.
Wait, no, we've got to get out.
( door opens, then closes )
Come and get it.
You're all going to like this...
( shrieks )
( glasses breaking )
SANDY:
There.
That ought to do it.
If you all needed water,
you should have asked.
I propose a toast:
To new friends!
Hold on a second.
I hope you all like
your tea strong.
Drink up!
( both slurping )
ALL:
Ah!