Tonight is going to be awesome
I can't believe they're going to show it!
TV is finally gonna
acknowledge our existence.
What are you talking about?
-Only Cutey Pets.
-The number-one pet show on TV.
They're gonna show this photo!
Pet? I thought you preferred
Animal Companions?
Oh, who cares about moral principles?
This is TV we're talking about!
I'm pretty excited, too.
Win Or Don't Win is calling tonight.
All I have to do is answer one question
and I'll win a new microwave.
What's wrong with our microwave?
Yeah, that makes sense.
Well, I can't wait to watch Daisy tonight.
You're going to meet Sally the snake,
aren't you, Daisy?
Yes, I am.
[sighs] I can't wait till 8:00.
Well, then I guess
it's whoever gets to the remote first!
Uh-bup-bup-bup! I've been up all night
saving my seat for...
[in Spanish] The great ending
of Sorrow Street.
[in English] And just to make sure
no one changes the channel,
I've hidden the remote!
Can I please watch Daisy?
-No!
This face was made for TV!
I don't want to grow a third arm
next time I make a cup of coffee!
I wish I had enough money
to buy my own remote!
OK, well, you know what?
I'm going... grocery shopping!
Hey! We're not done with you yet.
Wake up!
Wait a minute. We don't need the remote.
We can change the channel on the TV.
[gasps] You mean get up from the sofa
and change it manually,
like they did in ancient times
when people weren't lazy?
That sounds a little extreme, man.
[Gumball] Check, check.
OK, control, I'm going in.
[mimicking radio signal]
[Darwin] OK. [mimicking radio signal]
How you feeling?
[Gumball]
To be honest, I'm feeling pretty lazy.
[Darwin mimicking radio signal]
Keep going. You're doing great.
Something's happening.
It's like,
no one's ever walked here before.
I... I... I can't do it.
-I'm gonna turn around!
-[Darwin] No!
You've got to keep going!
You've passed the Christmas carpet stain.
There won't be enough willpower
to send you back.
OK. I'll try.
[grunts] Gravity pulling me down!
I'm not gonna make it!
I... can't... be...
bothered!
Abort the mission!
I repeat, abort the mission!
I'm sorry, buddy, but it wasn't possible.
Now I know why remotes were invented.
Here, take this.
It'll make you feel better.
Did I hear chocolate?
Yes.
And we'll give you some
when you tell us where the remote is!
-No! Never!
-Oh, really?
Not even for the chocolate
choo-choo train?
I'll get it!
Anais, I need you to tell me
what brand the TV is.
OK. But does this mean
I can watch Daisy tonight?
No, it means you won't be grounded
for six months.
What? But I'm four!
That's like one-eight of my life!
Then you don't want
to spend it locked up in your bedroom.
[grunts] Fine!
The train will not be stopping
at this mouth.
OK! OK!
Just give me the chocolate,
and I'll tell you!
-Yes!
[sighs] But in the form of a riddle.
The remote is in the valley
betwixt two hills.
It's name begins with a "B,"
ends with two T's,
and has "U" in the middle.
And you'll never find it! [laughing]
I know this one! I know this one!
Dude, there's no remote here.
Hmm. Wait a minute.
B-U-T-T.
It's under his butt, isn't it?
-[door opens]
-I got him! Get the remote!
[gasps] Where is it?
I've been sitting on it all day long!
There's only one person
that could have taken it.
Yeah! You!
Because it definitely wasn't me!
Where did you put it?
Dude, say it, don't spray it!
Tell him where it is!
-Tell him where it is now!
-Where did you put it?
Chill, everybody!
I meant Anais. It could only be Anais.
Oh... 'Cause we both want to watch
the same thing.
Yeah, right.
Get her!
[all three] Where's the remote?
-What remote?
-Right!
What are you doing?
Look! The scissors
she used to cut a hole in the sofa.
What are you talking about?
Tell us where it is!
Or Daisy won't have to worry
about headaches ever again.
No, please! Wait!
Here it is.
I'm sorry.
But I just want you to know...
I'm doing this for your own good!
No...
-All right, Daisy's getting it.
-No.
There is another.
-Another what?
-Another remote.
Mom went downtown to buy one.
[gasp] It's 20 to 8:00!
We need to get that remote!
-Thanks for the tip!
-Daisy!
Oh, yeah.
Wait. You're not coming?
I don't care about your stupid TV anymore!
All I need is my Daisy.
Gotcha.
Get her!
Get the remote!
Looking for these?
Thank you.
No!
[in Spanish] I've got to know if Consuelo
survives the pressure.
[in English] She's gaining on us!
-That remote is mine!
-Then come and get it!
Let's take the stairs.
She's getting away!
If you leave without paying,
you're setting a bad example
for your children!
I can't find the right change!
Oh, no.
Come on.
Thank you for being a responsible citizen.
[panting] Come on, dude.
Cutey Pets starts in five minutes.
[in Spanish] Sorrow Street
starts in five minutes.
[Nicole] [in English] Oh, no, it doesn't!
Win Or Don't Win does!
Give it, give it to me!
"I'm a celebrity"!
-Wait a minute!
-That's mine! Hey!
This isn't a TV remote.
Why?
My car!
Dagnabbit! It's for a garage door!
-What did you buy this for?
-What?
It's the one Anais told me to get.
Why would Anais tell you
to buy the wrong...
remote?
She planned this whole thing
from the start.
First, she gave Mom the idea
to buy a new remote.
I wish I had enough money
to buy my own remote!
[Nicole] So, when I called, she must have
given me the name of a garage-door opener.
Fine. Let me have a look.
-It's a Logikar 2000.
-Thanks, honey.
-[Richard] She overheard my riddle...
-I know this one!
[Richard] ...waited till you guys
were at Butt Valley
and cut a hole in the sofa
so she could take the real remote.
[Nicole] And the remote she smashed
upstairs must have been a decoy.
Which means the real one
must still be in the house.
[gasps] I had it in my hands.
-[Gumball] Thanks for the tip.
-Daisy!
Oh, yeah.
All I need is my Daisy.
I wish I had enough money
to buy my own remote!
All I need is my Daisy.
Logikar.
And I don't watch the stupid TV anymore.
I feel so proud of her,
yet really scared at the same time.
-No!
♪ Daisy, Daisy ♪